<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Preparing VPC and EC2 :: My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://example.org/2-prerequiste/2.1-createec2/index.html</link>
    <description>In this step, we will need to create a VPC with 2 public / private subnets. Then create 1 EC2 Instance Linux located in the public subnet, 1 EC2 Instance Windows located in the private subnet.&#xA;The architecture overview after you complete this step will be as follows:&#xA;To learn how to create EC2 instances and VPCs with public/private subnets, you can refer to the lab:</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/2-prerequiste/2.1-createec2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chuẩn bị VPC và EC2</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2-prerequiste/2.1-createec2/_index.vi/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/2-prerequiste/2.1-createec2/_index.vi/index.html</guid>
      <description>Trong bước này, chúng ta sẽ cần tạo một VPC có 2 subnet public / private. Sau đó tạo 1 EC2 Instance Linux nằm trong public subnet, 1 EC2 Instance Windows nằm trong private subnet.&#xA;Tổng quan kiến trúc sau khi các bạn hoàn tất bước này sẽ như sau:&#xA;Để tìm hiểu cách tạo các EC2 instance và VPC với public/private subnet các bạn có thể tham khảo bài lab :</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create VPC</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2-prerequiste/2.1-createec2/2.1.1-createvpc/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/2-prerequiste/2.1-createec2/2.1.1-createvpc/index.html</guid>
      <description>Create VPC Lab VPC Go to VPC service management console Click Your VPC. Click Create VPC. At the Create VPC page. In the Name tag field, enter Lab VPC. In the IPv4 CIDR field, enter: 10.10.0.0/16. Click Create VPC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Public Subnet</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2-prerequiste/2.1-createec2/2.1.2-createpublicsubnet/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/2-prerequiste/2.1-createec2/2.1.2-createpublicsubnet/index.html</guid>
      <description>Create Public Subnet Click Subnets. Click Create subnet. At the Create subnet page. In the VPC ID section, click Lab VPC. In the Subnet name field, enter Lab Public Subnet. In the Availability Zone section, select the first Availability zone. In the field IPv4 CIRD block enter 10.10.1.0/24.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Private Subnet</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2-prerequiste/2.1-createec2/2.1.3-createprivatesubnet/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/2-prerequiste/2.1-createec2/2.1.3-createprivatesubnet/index.html</guid>
      <description>Create Private Subnet Click Subnets. Click Create subnet. At the Create subnet page. In the VPC ID section, click Lab VPC. In the Subnet name field, enter Lab Private Subnet. In the Availability Zone section, select the first Availability zone. In the field IPv4 CIRD block enter 10.10.2.0/24.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create security groups</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2-prerequiste/2.1-createec2/2.1.4-createsecgroup/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/2-prerequiste/2.1-createec2/2.1.4-createsecgroup/index.html</guid>
      <description>Create security groups In this step, we will proceed to create the security groups used for our instances. As you can see, these security groups will not need to open traditional ports to ssh like port 22 or remote desktop through port 3389.&#xA;Create security group for Linux instance located in public subnet Go to VPC service management console Click Security Group. Click Create security group.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Public instance</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2-prerequiste/2.1-createec2/2.1.5-createec2linux/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/2-prerequiste/2.1-createec2/2.1.5-createec2linux/index.html</guid>
      <description>Go to EC2 service management console Click Instances. Click Launch instances. On the Step 1: Choose an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) page. Click Select to select AMI Amazon Linux 2 AMI. On the Step 2: Choose an Instance Type page. Click on Instance type t2.micro. Click Next: Configure Instance Details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create Private Instance</title>
      <link>https://example.org/2-prerequiste/2.1-createec2/2.1.6-createec2windows/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/2-prerequiste/2.1-createec2/2.1.6-createec2windows/index.html</guid>
      <description>Go to EC2 service management console Click Instances. Click Launch instances. On the Step 1: Choose an Amazon Machine Image (AMI) page. Drag the mouse down. Click Select to select AMI Microsoft Windows Server 2019 Base. On the Step 2: Choose an Instance Type page. Click on Instance type t2.micro. Click Next: Configure Instance Details.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>